(Bernadette:)Oh, right.
Did you get your hair cut?
"No. I got them all cut."
(Bernadette:)Which is still
so funny.
(Raj:)And when you go
to a Chinese restaurant,
(Raj:)he always gets the same fortune
in his fortune cookie.
Right. "Help, I'm a prisoner
(Bernadette:)in a Chinese
fortune cookie factory."
(Howard:)Okay, I think that's enough
about me.
(Raj:)He's right. Let's make
fun of his mother.
"Howard, come rub my feet!
My corns are killing me!"
"Howard, help me
out of the tub!
I'm stuck again!"
(Leonard:)Coming.
(Leonard:)Hey, lovebug.
(Penny:)Shut up.
(Penny:)You know what I've been doing
for the last hour?
(Leonard:)Mm, dreamily doodling
"Mrs. Leonard Hofstadter"
(Leonard:)in a notebook?
(Penny:)Listening to my father
go on and on
(Penny:)about what a great guy you are.
(Leonard:)You got to admit,
I am... I'm delightful.